== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Sheldon:)Who leaves their bike
in the hallway?
(Sheldon:)You know,
if I knew how to ride one,
(Sheldon:)I'd steal it.
(Leonard:)Ignore him,
(Leonard:)he's just cranky because Bert
from the geology lab
(Leonard:)won a big grant.
(Penny:)Oh, I heard him
interviewed on the radio!
(Penny:)You know, when they
told him he won,
(Penny:)he didn't believe it,
but then he did believe it.
(Penny:)It was so funny.
(Sheldon:)Who listens
to the radio anymore?
(Amy:)Bert is studying the way
microbes in rocks
(Amy:)can survive in extreme
environmental conditions.
(Leonard:)They say it could be
a potential indicator
(Leonard:)of life on other planets.
(Penny:)You know what, I've met Bert.
(Penny:)Isn't he an indicator
of life on other planets?
(Sheldon:)You used to
make those jokes about me.
(Sheldon:)Now everything is
Bert, Bert, Bert!
(Amy:)You know, Sheldon,
(Amy:)maybe if you take the time
(Amy:)to actually
read Bert's research,
(Amy:)you'd be less bitter
about him winning.
(Sheldon:)You want me to read
(Sheldon:)a geology paper?